<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<blogpost>
  <blogtitle>Dynamic Blog Update!</blogtitle>
  <blogdate>04-04-2024</blogdate>
  <blogheader>
    <imgname>giphy.webp</imgname>
    <headeralt>Just a test! Hello :3</headeralt>
  </blogheader>
  <blogcontent>
    Howdy everyone! I'm glad to announce that my Neocities website is now dynamically able to update when I make a new blog post!
    The downside though... It uses more client-side JavaScript... I know... I'm sorry. But this is the
    best I could do under the limitations of not owning my own server (since y'know I'm a NEET and can't afford
    it after all...). Another thing, I know it's not necessarily "dynamic", as all it does is fetch data using JavaScript and then
    populates the HTML. But "dynamic" is the best word I could think of when describing how I no longer need to hardcode HTML
    anymore! I'm a programmer, not an English major LOL! Whatever, I'm just really happy this works! Anywho, I made a new 
    &lt;a href="https://github.com/NEETdemon"&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;GitHub&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;!
    My code is fully open source and you're more than welcome to take it, modify it, and sell it to your heart's content! If you
    do sell it though, give me a cut of the profits please... I hella need it right now LMAO! Anywho, let me show you around the
    GitHub, and the code on how my site works!
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/NEETdemon/neetdemon-blog-data/main/img/dynamic_blog/neetdemon_github.png" alt="A picture of my GitHub profile" class="content-img" /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    So when you arrive to my GitHub profile, you should see two repos: "neetdemon-neocities-blog" and "neetdemon-blog-data".
    The repo, "neetdemon-neocities-blog", contains all the neocities website code (what you probably are currently using to view this post).
    It contains all the styling, and web design. The other repo, "neetdemon-blog-data", contains all the blog data, from images to the
    post content, blog post title, and the date it was created. 
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/NEETdemon/neetdemon-blog-data/main/img/dynamic_blog/blog_post_xml.png" alt="A picture of what each blog post XML file looks like" class="content-img" /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    Starting in "neetdemon-blog-data", each post is basically one big XML file. Since I need to use some HTML, I use decoded tags as a replacement
    for special character such as "<" or ">" to prevent any errors from happening when parsing the XML to HTML. It's a little tedious but I don't
    mind it.
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/NEETdemon/neetdemon-blog-data/main/img/dynamic_blog/neetdemon_github_blogjs.png" alt="A picture of the Javascript code on the blog index page." class="content-img" /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    Now going over to "neetdemon-neocities-blog", let's start by talking about `blog.js`. Without rambling too much and getting
    too into detail about it, all this file really does is fetch all the posts from "neetdemon-blog-data/index.xml". Then parses
    it to the HTML on `blog/index.html` using the JavaScript DOM. If an error occurs an alert pops up telling you
    to try again later. It creates a link to each individual blog post. Very simple, stuff if you ask me.
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/NEETdemon/neetdemon-blog-data/main/img/dynamic_blog/neetdemon_github_postjs.png" alt="A picture of the Javascript code on the blog index page." class="content-img" /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    Okay, this is the more complicated part to talk about, but last one, I promise! Anyways, assuming you clicked one of the links on
    `/blog/index.html`, you are sent to `/blog/post.html?title=some_blog_post_name`. This webpage uses `post.js` to fetch the current 
    blog post's content data from the "neetdemon-blog-data" repo on GitHub.
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    For this to work correctly, `post.html` requires a `title` parameter, otherwise the user is going to be redirected to `not_found.html`. 
    The `title` parameter in the URL, is a string that represents the filename of a blog post XML file in the "neetdemon-blog-data/post" repo.
    For example, this blog title is "Dynamic Blog Update!", but the filename itself is "dynamic_blog.xml". So there's another error that needs
    to be handled. If there's no filename under "neetdemon-blog-data/post", then the user will, again, be redirected to `not_found.html`.
    Another problem, whether the filename exists or not, if GitHub decides to stop allowing HTTP requests one day, or maybe some 
    sort of error that happens on GitHub's server-side occurs, an alert will pop up telling the user to try again later and the page 
    will remain blank. I'll make a custom page for 500 errors eventually but this was a lot of work for today.
    &lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
    So yeah, that's about it for the website update! There's more things to work on but I'm pretty much done for today. I'll get back to it
    tomorrow. Anyways, I'm SOOOOOO close to reaching 100 views on my neocities site! Thank you so much! I know it's not really a lot, but I 
    truly appreciate every view I get! Anyways, I still need to fix the `/index.html` to fetch all the latest blog posts, but I'll save that
    for tomorrow. It's currently 4:41AM as I'm typing this and I need to get some shut eye. I only ate once today, so I'm getting kinda eepy.
    If you read this far, thank you so much, and I hope you have a good day/afternoon/night! ^_^
  </blogcontent>
</blogpost>