<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<blogpost>
    <blogtitle>Fixed Index and Life Update</blogtitle>
    <blogdate>04-23-2024</blogdate>
    <blogheader>
        <imgname>FPbgKg.gif</imgname>
        <headeralt>Gif from the anime Welcome to the NHK, of Tatsuhiro grabbing a tissue while on his computer and boxes tumbling over</headeralt>
    </blogheader>
    <blogcontent>
        Okay, I know I've said in the previous blog post I was going to fix the issue... but I FINALLY did it! If you don't know what I'm talking about, 
        I finally made it to where it grabs all the latest blogs I made to the `index.html` file. So yeah, yippee!!! Okay website, update over LMAO.
        &lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        I just got back from visiting my friend `S`'s house for his b-day with some other friends of ours. He's basically my brother at this point since I've known 
        him and his family for a while now, and even lived with them since we were renting from the same land-lady. We were supposed to visit `S` during his 
        actual b-day, but unfortunately he was having some mental issues at the time. Anyways, we went to a taco truck around the corner of his house, and it 
        was delicious!.. but there was a problem... Everyone but `S` got food poisoning. I was the first one to go since I have a fast metabolism. I ended up 
        in the bathroom yacking out all the food and even fell asleep since my head was spinning and my stummy was hurting. They ended up playing Halo while I 
        was knocked the fuck out. Afterwards all I know is, it was time to go home. But ended up going to my other friend's house instead since he was my ride 
        back. The next morning one of my friends ended up yacking, and my friend who was my ride had to go to the bathroom multiple times.
        &lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        On more depressing news, the friend that I'm living with, his family told me that we're probably going to have to move out sooner than expected. 
        Then they told me that I should probably go try to find a job to where I plan on moving to next. I'm so lost and overwhelemed on what to do right now... 
        I should probably update my sister on what's going to happen but I'm too embarassed. Fuck my life... I thought building a Trading bot was going to be 
        simple, but it ended up get fucked by trading fees, and all the places I applied to never got back to me (not even a denial). Things are getting really 
        scary really quickly. I miss when things were simple. Anyways I'm coding up another project using Zig as the programming language. I can't go too into 
        detail about the project but it's both a fun and stressful experience since there is a lack of documentation on the lang. 
        &lt;br /&gt;
        &lt;br /&gt;
        Anyways, I hope you guys are having a better and cozier time than me right now. Being a high-tech low life isn't easy right now (especially if you're 
        looking for a job). But enough espresso depresso! I'ma keep it moving! Fuck it, we ball! On a less depressive note, I'm almost at 200 views on my 
        Neocities! I gotta see if it's actual views or if it's web crawlers now that I think of it... but if it's real people then thank you so much! I have 
        a few things cooking up for you guys and I hope you guys are gonna like it! Alright you guys, I'm off to work on my programming project, I'll ttyl! 
        Cheers!
    </blogcontent>
</blogpost>